const quiz = {
    topic: 'CSS',
    questions: [
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is NOT a valid CSS unit?',
            options: ['cm', 'em', 'in', 'pt'],
            correctAnswer: 'pt'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property sets the spacing between lines of text?',
            options: ['line-height', 'font-size', 'text-align', 'text-decoration'],
            correctAnswer: 'line-height'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to change the color of text?',
            options: ['font-style', 'color', 'text-decoration', 'font-weight'],
            correctAnswer: 'color'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is NOT a CSS positioning property?',
            options: ['position', 'top', 'bottom', 'margin'],
            correctAnswer: 'margin'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to create a border around an element?',
            options: ['padding', 'border', 'margin', 'outline'],
            correctAnswer: 'border'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to add background color or image to an element?',
            options: ['background-color', 'color', 'border', 'margin'],
            correctAnswer: 'background-color'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to control the amount of space between the content and the border of an element?',
            options: ['padding', 'border-spacing', 'margin', 'line-height'],
            correctAnswer: 'padding'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to change the font of an element?',
            options: ['font-size', 'font-family', 'font-weight', 'text-transform'],
            correctAnswer: 'font-family'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to create columns in a web page?',
            options: ['column-count', 'column-width', 'column-gap', 'column-rule'],
            correctAnswer: 'column-count'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to align text within an element?',
            options: ['text-align', 'vertical-align', 'line-height', 'text-indent'],
            correctAnswer: 'text-align'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to change the size of an element?',
            options: ['width', 'height', 'size', 'scale'],
            correctAnswer: 'width'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which property is used to make text bold?',
            options: ['font-weight', 'font-style', 'text-transform', 'text-decoration'],
            correctAnswer: 'font-weight'
        }
    ]
}

export default quiz;